你的气色很差,伙计
You look like shit,man.
我没事
I'm all right.
你就嘴硬吧
Keep telling yourself that.
这个?
That right there?
这是本市有史以来 最好的家庭作业了
That is the best homework assignment the city ever came up with.
是啊 我和孩子周末就去
Yeah.Me and the kid start this weekend.
除非又被阿曼达拦着了
That is,of course,unless Amanda botches everything up,like she always does.
我可以让莫妮卡给她打个电话 她们关系一直很好
I could have Monica give her a call.They always got along pretty well.
谢谢你的好意,不过你最好还是别管
You know,Eddie,I appreciate it,but it's best if you stay out of it.
马克,什么事?
Yo,D'Mac,what's up?
我有兴趣 你有什么情况?
Yeah,I'm interested.What do you got?
海底人 Boyle Heights区
Haitians.Boyle Heights.
我知道那个地方
Yeah,I know the place.
3-B,知道了
3-B,got it.
有毒品正在交易
Ya yo changing hands.
你真想招惹这个混蛋?
You really wanna mess with this low-level shit?
对,我们走
Yeah,let's go.
- 情况不错?- 一切都好
- Are we good?- All signs point to it.
你们谁签收?
Which one of you gentlemen is gonna sign for this?
衣服不错
Nice suit.
听说卫生间堵了?
I heard there was a problem with the toilet?
好了 我们还有不到一小时 动身吧
All right,fellas.We got less than one hour.Let's go.
走开
Move.
- 警察,不许动!- 妈的!
- Police,freeze!- Shit!
- 抓住他!- 趴在地上!
- Get him!- On the floor,God damn it!
别跑!
Stop!
不许动!
Don't move!
- 抓住他了吗?- 他跑了
- You got him?- He got away.
- 什么?- 他跑了!
- What?- He got away!
该死的!
Shit!
别说话,杰克 什么都别说!
Not a word,Welles.Not a goddamn word!
混蛋!
Son of a bitch!
行动
Now.
怎么
What the...
队长 电梯出故障了
Chief.We got a problem with the elevators.
- 趴下!- 别起来!
- Get down!- And stay down!
注意了,都给我趴在地上!
Now that I have your attention,get on the floor,right now!
- 都趴下 - 别激动!
- Take it easy,take it easy.- Everyone!
- 你也趴下!
- You,too,come on!- Get down!
都显示 "出现故障"
Everything's reading "Malfunction."
- 怎么回事?- 不知道
- The hell is this?- I don't know.
我们不想伤人!
We're not here to hurt you!
老老实实的就不会有事,听见了吗?
You stay calm,you go home for dinner,you understand me?
别看我
Don't look at me.
都不许动!趴在地板上!
Nobody move!And get down on the floor!
别叫!
Shut up!
有人不老实啊
We got a naughty one here.
天!FedCal银行
Jesus!FedCal,the bank.
不听话的女孩 现在只能打个电话了
All right,that's it,bad girl.Now we get to go make a phone call.
45分了!
Forty-five!
- 14新闻频道热线- 就说正在发生抢劫
- News 14 hotline.- Tell them there's a robbery in progress.
我在洛杉矶市区的FedCal银行
I'm from the FedCal Bank,downtown LA.
正发生抢劫案
There's a robbery in progress.
- 劫匪还在银行吗?- 还在
- Are they still in the bank?- They're still...
劫匪
Are they...
我们快走吧
Come on,man,let's get out of here.
我们走!
Let's go!
跳!
Jump!
趴下!
Get down!
各位,发生银行抢劫案 我们去市区
Hey,guys,a bank robbery.We're headed downtown.
这就去!
Let's go,now!
- 我在处理!
- I got the back!- I'm on it!
他们走楼梯离开的!
They left the bank using the stairs!
所有出口已封锁
All exits are covered.
看,楼顶上,有个警卫在那里降落!
Look,on the roof,a guard!Land it!
- 我们没得到许可 - 我们是最先到现场的 快降落
- We're not cleared for this.- We're first on the scene.Land us,now.
走吧!
Let's go!
拿出摄像机
Get the camera out.
你怎么样?
Are you okay?
- 趴在地上!
- No!- Get on the ground!
趴在地上!马上下直升机!
Get on the ground!Get out of the chopper now!
也趴在地上!
Take a seat next to your friends!
真是一群笨蛋!好样的
What a bunch of dummies!Good boy.
只有一个能干的摄影师!
Nothing but glorified paparazzi!
我们走吧!
Get us out of here!
14频道走错路了
There goes Channel 14 going the wrong way.
所以他们总是最后到现场
That's why they're in last place.
里弗斯,你自由了
Come on,Rivers,you're a free man.
可以走了
You're out of here.
有空楼层吗?
Any vacant floors?
26层正在装修
Yeah,26 is under construction.
那一层有摄像头吗?
You got security cameras on that floor?
装修时候不会有
Not in the construction area.
让法医去检查一下
Have forensics go over it.
你要调取很多人的指纹
You'll pick up prints from half the damn city.
但也没办法
Do it anyway.
- 没问题 - 好
- You got it.- Okay.
跑很快 成员复杂
Went down pretty fast.We got a mixed crew.
其中一个人有外地口音
Apparently,one of the guys had some type of an accent.
- 抢走了多少钱?- 200多万
- How much did they take?- North of two million.
有的钞票可能有记号
Some of the bills might be marked.
说不定能因此找到
Who knows,maybe we'll get lucky.
劫匪用C4炸药破坏了电梯
So,they used C-4 to knock out the elevators.
残留物送去化验了
Residue's being sent to the lab now.
谢谢 自动步枪,时间计算精确
Thanks.Automatic weapons,precision timing.
定向爆破 其中难度可想而知
Shape charges.Degree of difficulty is off the charts.
毫无疑问,他们是高手
They were hot shit,no doubt about that.
抓住高手 感觉才更爽
It'll make it that much sweeter when we take them down.
是啊
Yeah.
什么事?
What is it you want?
你是谢尔盖吗?
You Sergei?
监狱里的米哈伊洛维奇让我来的
Mikhail,from in the joint,sent me.
好
Okay.
你们正在玩啊?
Y'all having fun,huh?
别动,小子
Not so fast,my man.
出示证件
Show me ID.
美国!美国!
USA!USA!USA!
老实点
Think about it.
别冲动
Cool down.
我们有伏特加 有事好商量?
We...We have vodka and take care of business,huh?
估计你会这么说
That's what I thought you'd say.
我们有了一大笔钱
We've got some serious stacks now.
真是爽啊
And I mean it's love,baby.
- 还行吧 - 得了
- Yeah,we did all right.- All right,my ass.
这是我们最大的一笔抢劫,你看起来并不怎么高兴
Our biggest heist yet,and you,you don't seem too jazzed.
我挺高兴
No,I'm good.
挺高兴
I'm good.
爸爸昨晚打电话了
Listen,Dad called last night.
让我们去探望他
He wants us to come see him.
不行 杰克
No.Hell,no,Jake.
我在监狱里见过爸爸 我去过少管所
I've been to see Dad in jail.I've been to juvie.
我再也不去监狱了 不管是为了你,为了爸爸,
I'm not going back.Not for you,not for Dad,
- 还是为了任何人 决不 - 好,好
- not for anybody.Ever.- Okay,okay.
他还有不到五年刑期
He's got less than five.
他出来以后,
So,when he gets out,
我们给他盖个房子
maybe we build him a house.
- 行吗?- 行
- Cool?- Cool.
戈登说看见有记号的钞票,就烧掉
Gordon says you find anything marked,burn it.
弹得不错
Sounds tight.
让你弟弟和那么多钱在一块 你能放心?
You just gonna leave your kid bro up there with all that paper?
他要是花光了,你打死他就是
If he runs out with it,shoot him.
我正有此意
I will,too.
记得这首曲子吗?
Remember the song?
好
All right.
我不知道怎么说 我们 很忙 你看看
I don't know what to tell you.We're so...We're so busy.Look at this.
假如把隔壁的空房子一起买过来,这个家该多美啊
And if we get that empty space next door,think about how amazing it's gonna be.
- 这是什么?- 打开看看
- What's this?- Open it.
天啊
Oh,my God.
真好看
It's beautiful.
你也一样好看
I think you're beautiful,too.
如果你愿意,
If you'll have me,
我想和你共度一生
I wanna spend the rest of my life with you.
狂妄的家伙
Cocky assholes.
录像准备好了
Tapes are ready.
看看
All right,let's see what we got.
大厅共有20部电梯
There's 20 elevators for the lobby.
较低楼层12部,较高楼层8部
Twelve for the lower floors,eight for the uppers.
以22楼为界
You can cross over at 22.
一天之中,有多少人上下电梯?
So,over the course of the day,how many people on and off?
- 1万左右
- Ten thousand,give or take.- Shit.
只看谁在装修楼层下电梯
Well,let's see who got off on the construction floor.
肯定没几个人
It couldn't have been more than a handful of people.
这没办法 录像是根据时间来的,不是根据楼层来的
Well,it doesn't work that way.These tapes are time-coded,not floor-coded.
这么多人上下电梯
All these people getting on and off
我们却不知道停在几楼?
and we have no idea what floor we're watching?
是这样的
Yeah.I mean,that's how it works.
你们的监控录像可真行啊
Come on.This is some system you got here,Chief.
别人的大楼基本都这样
Most of the buildings in the city are set up this way.
- 这么设计,真是白痴 - 这话我不爱听!
- Whoever set it up is an idiot.- Hey,I don't need this!
我可是好心来帮忙
All right,I'm down here trying to help.
他这话不是有意的?
Hey.Look,man,he doesn't mean nothing by it,all right?
- 谢谢你前来?- 你去死吧
- Thanks for coming by,okay?- Screw you.
是你的药不管用 还是缺少女人了?
Meds not working or we just need to get you laid?
- 你怎么了?- 你看
- What's the problem?- Look at this.
这是摄像头 他们知道电梯里没人
It's a camera.They knew the elevator was empty.
他们对大楼了如指掌
They knew the building.They knew the whole system.
即使看上100个小时
Yeah,must be a hundred hours here.
我们也看不出什么名堂
We don't know what the hell we're looking for.
大开曼岛不是不好,
Not to piss on Grand Cayman,
不过我觉得把钱存在安的列斯群岛的话
but I think I can get you an additional 75 basis points
收益能增加75个百分点?
in the Dutch Antilles.I say why not?
不过市场不断变动,
Yeah,but the way the markets keep jumping around,man,
谁能知道几周之后利率是多少?
another four,six weeks,who knows what the rates'll be?
你看过最新的财经报告了吗?
And have you seen the latest Bloomberg report?
- 那里经济形势不好 - "财经报告"?得了吧?
- Shit is bleak out there.- "Bloomberg reports"?Are you kidding me?
大学生 别想得太多了
Come on,college guys.Let's not over-think it.
是啊 既然安的列斯群岛给的利率更高
Yeah,come on.Dutch Antilles wanna pay us more money.
- 还考虑什么 - 我喜欢安的列斯群岛,
- That's a no-brainer.- I like the Dutch Antilles,
只要银行别在一夜之间破产了就行
as long as the banks don't pack up and take my money overnight.
还是把10％的钱捐给慈善机构?
Of course.10% to the usual charities?
- 当然 - 我同意
- Absolutely.- Cool by me.
我租了一架飞机 今晚在凡奈斯机场起飞
I chartered a jet.It's taking off Van Nuys Airport tonight.
谁想和我一起走的话,这里有专用通行证
Anybody wants to come,I got your private parking passes right here.
这就妥了
It'll be sweet.
现在感觉人生真好
Man,life's looking pretty good from right here.
我考虑一下
I'll let you know later.
好房子 好视野
Nice house.Cool view.
好酒
Great scotch.
劫持了新闻台的直升机 上面写满了"AJ"
You know,jacking that news chopper had "A.J." written all over it.
你怎么进来的?
How'd you get in my house?
太简单了
Please.
你提前出狱了?
They let you out early or what?
表现良好 提前一年释放
Good behavior.About a year early.
不过你们都把我忘了吧?
But I guess you guys kind of lost track,huh?
我们说过彼此不联系 你来什么事?
No contact.That's what we agreed upon.So,what's up?
我想再喝一杯
I think I'm gonna have another scotch.
这是好酒 一起喝吧?
It's good shit,John.You gonna drink with me,right?
当然
Sure you are.
我之所以来找你,
You see,I came to you,John,
因为你的觉悟比他们高
because you the one with that higher consciousness and shit.
- 接着说 - 你问我有什么事
- All right,I'm listening.- Well,you asked what's up.
我就是想你了
I miss my homies.That's what's up.
此外还有一些旧账
That,and some unfinished business.
04年抢劫案你的那份钱 都给你留着
Your money from '04 is safe and accruing interest.
账号在戈登那里
Gordon's got the bank account numbers.
莉莉呢?她在谁那里?
What about Lilli?Who's got her numbers?
她现在和杰克恋爱
She's with Jake now.
我祝福他们 我有件事要谈谈
Well,good for them.I got a deal we need to discuss.
- 一笔买卖 - 开什么玩笑?
- A job.- You're kidding me,right?
你因为有买卖来找我?
You're coming at me with a job right now?
难道我是来闲聊的吗?
Think I'd come at you on some bullshit?
这是难得的机会,约翰 你了解我这人
Once in a lifetime,John.You know me.
我研究过了
I do my homework.
你想让我说什么?
All right,so what do you want me to say here?
什么都不用说
You ain't got to say shit.
只要记住我是04年抢劫案中 唯一在楼梯上受伤被捕的人
Just remember I was the one left bleeding on that fire escape in '04.
警察对我用尽了办法
And they tried everything they could to flip me.
我也没交代, 因为我遵守我们的协议
I ain't budge,'cause we had a deal.I kept my end.
还留着这道伤疤 我对你有恩
I kept this,too.You owe me,bro.
对你们都有恩
All of you.
我和戈登当年收你入队的时候
What were you,boosting Camaros back in Riverside
你也就是个小混混吧?
when me and Gordon decided to let you in?
别看不起我
So,don't be so quick to write me off.
那好,我和他们谈谈 明天再联系你
All right,I'll talk to the boys and I'll get back at you tomorrow.
这就好 我喜欢你家
You do that.Love the place.
不过警报器太差
Alarm system sucks,though.
你来了
There she is.
我的兄弟 你好吗?
Hello.How's my baby G doing?
我挺好
I'm good,I'm fine.
- 你气色不错 - 我感觉不错
- You look good.- I feel good.
- 是吗?- 是的
- Yeah?Yeah?- Yeah.
医生说你可能下周就结束戒毒
They tell me maybe you finish the program next week.
这八周很难熬
It's been a tough eight weeks.
放心 这次我肯定能戒掉
Don't worry.I'm gonna do it this time.
我这么想也这么感觉
That's what my mind and my body's telling me.
我支持你 你知道的吧?
I'm with you.I'm with you.You know that,right?
- 我不再需要毒品了
- Yeah?- I'm not gonna need these anymore.
我离开戒毒所的时候,
By the time I leave here,
就彻底没有毒瘾了
I'm gonna be cleaner than the day I was born.
你知道我很感谢你吧?
You know I'm grateful,don't you?
行了 你也就嘴上这么说说
Stop it.You don't need to say that to me,all right?
- 我的信带来了吗?- 当然
- Did you get my letter?- Yeah,sure did.
我一直在念叨
I've been non-stop tripping over this,I tell you.
- 加勒比海?- 看看海水
- Caribbean,huh?- Look at the water.
清澈湛蓝 既温暖又凉爽
Clear and blue.Cool and warm at the same time.
我只想回到那里
I've just got to get back there.
等你离开戒毒所,我亲自带你去
Soon as you're out of here,I'm gonna take you there myself.
- 我保证 - 好
- I promise.- All right.
我爱你
I love you.
关掉
Turn that off.
我回到家
I know,so I walk into my house.
看见他在我家里,喝着酒
He's standing there,he's drinking my whiskey.
我正想开枪的
I was gonna shoot him in the back of his head.
开枪就对了
Should've shot him.
这家伙刚出来一天,就想干一笔
The guy's been out 24 hours,already wants to do a job.
- 真是疯了 - 我看是有胆量
- He's crazy.- Or he's got huge balls.
对抢钱的事 老鬼肯定心里有底
Yeah,Ghost doesn't play when it comes to money.
他一向不含糊
He's too smart for that.
- 这混蛋没那么精明 - 一定的
- The bastard's not that smart.- That's for sure.
也就有点小聪明
He's clever,not smart.
我们总是隔一年才能干一笔
You guys,we always wait at least a year between jobs.
- 说明比不上他 - 戈登你和他交往多年吧?
- There's a reason for that.- Gordon,you guys go way back,right?
他可靠吗?
Think he's being straight up?
当年他完全可以供出我们,
Ghost could've ratted us out a long time ago,
但他守口如瓶
but he didn't.Kept his word.
等他的那份钱拿到手 那就难说了?
What's to stop him from doing exactly that once we give him his cut from '04?
- 问题就在这里
- See,that's the problem.- Yeah.
- 这是大问题 - 肯定有什么不对
- That's a big problem there.- Something ain't right.
- 我信不过他 - 放心
- I don't trust him.- Relax.
- 他会带来麻烦 - 我觉得他盘算好了
- He's trouble.- I think he's onto something,though.
- 他说这是一笔大买卖 - 我不管他怎么说?
- He says it's big.- Do I look like I care what he says?
你们决定吧,我都会赞成
Well,whatever you decide to do,I'm down with you.
- 我去阁楼
- All right.- I'm going to the loft.
私人派对!
Private party!
- 你去哪儿?- 你管不着!
- Where you going?- None of your damn business!
- 你们好 - 莉莉
- Gentlemen.- It's Lilli.
- 谁要的酒?- 这是送给约翰的
- Baby,who ordered the Dom?- That's for Johnny-boy.
酒吧那个穿绿衣服的女孩送的
It's the girl in the green at the bar.
她很漂亮
She's cute.
- 别让她掏钱 - 不行,她要付出代价
- Don't let her pay for it.- No,no,she's gonna pay,man.
这就对了 你们看我的
This is how it's done.Let me show you.
急什么,大学生 这又不是大学宿舍
Slow down,lvy League.This ain't the frat house,man.
你可真能取笑
Well,that's some funny shit,man.That's some funny shit.
我去去就回
I'll come back up later.
- 老鬼 - 久违了
- Ghost.- It's been a long time,girl.
- 你什么时候出来的?- 怎么想我了?
- When did you get out?- Why?You miss me?
老鬼 别纠缠她
Ghost.You need to back up.
你激动什么 杰克
Easy,Jake.Easy.
我真心希望你们幸福 我和她的事都是以前了
I wish you guys the best.Really.It's the past.
我来谈论的是未来
I'm here to discuss the future.
别介意
If I may.
我说过明天联系你,老鬼
Told you tomorrow,Ghost.
我不是来扫你们兴的 只为了正事
I'm not here to bust any balls.Just business.
没别的
All right
AJ 又纹身了吗?
A.J.Any new tats?
- 纹了几个 - 我也是
- Yeah,man,couple.- Me,too.
- 戈登 - 老鬼
- G.- Ghost.
一向可好?
How's my man?
我很好,哥们
I'm doing good,mate.
气氛有点紧张啊?
Lot of tension in the room,huh?
你有何事?
What do you want,Ghost?
真是的
Goddamn.
现在就说?
It's like that?
现在就说
It's like that.
那我简单说说
Well,I'll be brief.
简单说就像“偷天换日”中的大买卖
Let's say we go Italian Job on that ass.
我们上楼谈吧?
Why don't we take this upstairs,Ghost?
好的
Fair enough.
和以前的计划一样 2500―3000万美元
Same plan as before,gentlemen.25 to 30 mil.
这就是能到手的钱 不过要抓紧
All the cash we can carry.Got to move fast,though.
"抓紧," 是什么时间?
When you say "fast," how fast?
下周二
Next Tuesday.
什么?
What?
老鬼,你让我们5天之内去抢一辆运钞车?
Ghost,you want us to take down an armored truck in five days?
要先搞到路线图才行,
I mean,it's not even worth talking about unless you got the route,
况且路线还经常变动
and they change the route all the time.
- 我们上次就是因此失手的 - 你有路线图吗?
- That's what screwed us last time.- Yeah,man,you got the route?
有 正是下周二的路线图
I got it.Exact one from next Tuesday.
还有什么问题?
Any more questions?
- 你怎么得到的?- 在监狱里
- How'd you get it?- In the joint.
我和一个俄国人交好
I got in good with this Russian.
保护他不受别的囚犯欺负
Had the pleasure of keeping them guys from Compton off his ass.
作为回报,他让监狱外的同伙
In exchange,he had his comrades on the outside
收买了调度员
put the arm down on the dispatcher.
让调度员做内奸,
So the dispatcher do anything to screw the job up,
他在乌克兰的家人都被害了
they're wiping out his whole family back at the Ukraine.
也包括牧羊犬
Down to the sheepdog.
我们凭什么信任这个俄国人?
Why should we trust the Russians?
他们喜欢自己的牧羊犬
They love their sheepdogs.
不说笑话了,
All bullshit aside,
事成之后除去俄国人的份额 还有2500万美元
I'm in for a quarter mil with the Russians out my cut when the job's done.
这你们不用管,
It's not your concern,
不必相信俄国人 相信自己的贪婪
so don't trust the Russians.Trust greed.
- 我们凭什么相信你?- 真是的,AJ
- Why should we trust you?- Well,shit,A.J.
我刚放出来 肯定不急着回去
I'm fresh out.I ain't in no hurry to go back.
再说了,我干嘛要害自己人呢?
Besides,why would I screw over my guys?
况且我的钱还在你手里呢?
Especially when you're holding all my money,right?
那你有什么计划?
Okay.What about the setup?
光有路线图还不行,还有很多准备工作
I mean,there's knowing the route,and then there's the logistics,you know.
杰克的担心不无道理 5天确实太短了
Five days.Jake's right.That's a real,real short fuse.
这就要靠你了
That's where you come in.
你和杰克合计一下 肯定会有办法的
But I trust that when you and Jake put your heads together,you'll figure it out.
不管干不干,今晚就给我回话
Either way,I need to know tonight.
不愿干的话,没问题
You ain't got the heart to pull it off,a'ight.
把上次的钱给我,我就走人
We'll settle up on the money you owe me,I'm sayonara.
占用你们的时间了 谢谢你的雪茄
Appreciate your time,gentlemen.Thanks for the cigar.
- 戈登,我们看看路线图 - 好
- Hey,G,let me check out that route.- Yeah.
这不是我们的风格 太仓促了
This is not the way we do things,gentlemen.It's too fast,it's too rushed.
钱虽然多,但是感觉很勉强
It's a lot of money,but this whole thing feels forced.
才5天?5天?
Five days?Five?
是的,只要计划好了就行
Yeah,man,but,you know,we can get the setup right.
风险大,获利就大
Bet big,win big.
这就是真理
It's the only way to play.
我们就是靠抢劫为生的人
We're takers,gents.That's what we do for a living.
我们吃这碗饭
We take.
这可是一大笔钱,杰克
It's a lot of money,Jake.
- 我们正是为了钱 - 你对此有把握?
- And that's what we're here for.- You sure about this?
如果调查可行的话
If it checks out.
如果可行,我干
If it checks out,I'm in.
- 什么事?- 有件事你可能有兴趣,
- Yeah,what's up?- Thought you'd wanna know,
你抓住的海地人
your Haitian buddy?
他的律师起诉你滥用暴力
His lawyerjust filed on you for excessive force.
他是个大汉,还不老实
All right.The guy was 6'5",he was resisting.
不用暴力怎么办?
What was I supposed to do?
那看来伤害他的感情了
Yeah,well,you must've hurt his feelings.
银行抢劫案的事  用来炸电梯的C4炸药调查的怎么样了?
The bank.Hey,listen,what about the C-4 they used to blow the elevators?
经过化验,是来自内华达州的一家采矿公司,
Well,from the taggants,forensics traced it to a mining company out of Nevada,
大约两月前被盗的
stolen about...About two months ago.
有记号的钞票呢?
All right.And what about the marked bills?
银行给出了清单 麦克斯马上就会传真一份
Bank finally sent over a list.Max is gonna fax out a memo right now.
听我说,
Listen,man,
已经好几周了你和阿曼达有联系吗?
it's been a couple of weeks now.You hear anDhing from Amanda?
谢谢你的关心,但我不需要帮助
Listen,I appreciate it,but I don't need any help.
我们自己能解决 不过也谢谢你
We can work it out on our own.But thanks.
那好 我挂了
All right.I'll talk to you later.
从老鬼的路线图上看
All right,so,for this route Ghost is talking about.
我们唯一的机会在这里
The only place we stand a chance is right there.
- 这是什么地方?- 原本是地铁中转站
- What's there?- It's an old subway car turnaround.
很大,和街道平行
It's large enough,and it runs parallel to the street.
合适得很 可以在希望大街,
It's kind of perfect.I mean,we can get access on Hope Street,
不过我觉得橄榄大街和第四大道路口更好
but I say we hold them up at Olive and Fourth.
嗯
All right.
我们要先去那里调查一下,
And we need to get down there first and get some intel on,
街道情况,车流量大小等等,不过看来问题不大
you know,street patterns,traffic density,that sort of thing,but it looks good.
确定好了爆炸范围和路面厚度,
Once we determine the blast radius and street density,
我就能算出需要多少C4炸药
I can tell you how much C-4 you're gonna need to score.
怎么脱身?
What about the exits?
正在研究
Work in progress,G.
我们先去调查一下,再说
You know,we got to get down there first,check it out.
- 想出几套脱身方案 - 没问题
- Give me some exits.- You got it.
- 干得很好 - 好
- It's good work.- Cool.
- 好了 - 好了
- All right,gang.- Good to go.
和以往一样 不难得手
Easy money,baby.Same as before.
钱都在前面的运钞车
All the cash is in the front truck.
后面那辆是空的 只是护航
Second truck's totally empty.Just an escort.
两辆车各有两人
Two men up front,two men in the back.
压动式12口径手枪 和40口径格洛克手枪
Pump action 12-gauge and.40 caliber Glocks.
或许是9毫米口径
Maybe 9mm.
他们的通讯设备可能改进了,
They may have upgraded their communication by now,
但是防弹玻璃没变
but the same standard bulletproof windows.
他们自以为万无一失
They ain't gonna know what hit them.
好了 先做上标记
Here we go.Must've taken up the tracks.
就这样
That's it.
他还做这种买卖
Yeah,he's still working it.
也买了辆新车
Got brand-new wheels to show for it,too.
我们走
All right,let's go.
等我的命令
All right,wait for my go-ahead.
- 早上好,弗朗克 车不错啊!- 你们干什么?
- Good morning,Franco.Nice wheels!- What do you guys want?
- 趴在车上
- Get up against the car.- Turn around.
喂,喂,我是清白的
Hey,hey,hey,hey,I'm clean,man.
别碰我 把你的车开走?
Hands off.All right?Why don't you move your car?
你知道内华达州被盗的C4炸药吗?
What do you know about some C-4 boosted out of Nevada?
我一点不知道
Nevada?I don't know nothing about that.
出了事,你不可能一点消息不知道
Come on,if it's guns or explosives,you heard something about it.
你若是再被捕,就要判十年
You know,you get busted again,you're facing 10 years minimum.
- 你知道吧?- 我知道这是公共场合
- You know that,right?- I know this is a public place.
我没干坏事 你们还是把车开走吧?
I ain't done nothing.So,why don't you move your car?
- 别胡闹了 - 哈奇
- Do me a favor.- Hey,Hatch.
- 你看看!- 什么情况?
- Look at this!- What you got?
- 怎么了?- 弗朗克
- What's that?- Come on,Franco.
- 你的车胎扎到钉子了
- It's a damn shame.- Looks like you caught a nail.
- 车胎瘪了 - 还是两下
- Yeah,you got a flat.- Twice.
- 拜托 - 后备箱里有备用轮胎吧?
- Come on.- You got a spare in the trunk,right?
- 来,我帮你换轮胎 - 要检查我的后备箱,
- Come on,I'll help you.Come on.- You wanna check my trunk,
先要有搜查证
why don't you go get yourselves a warrant?
调度处,第九大道和110街道路口有一辆车出了故障
Hey,Dispatch,we got a disabled vehicle on 9th and the 110.
多长时间能到这里?
How long would it take to get here?
我就在附近
Yeah,right around the corner.
哦,就在附近
You got one in the area.
真是巧啊 一会见
That's great.It's my lucky day.I'll see you in a minute.
你们以为我是傻子吗?
You guys must think I'm stupid or something,right?
- 开进来!- 搞什么啊?
- Bring it in!- Man,what the hell is this?
你们至少要用正当手段!
Come on!This has got to be illegal!
- 别给我下套!
- No.- Entrapment or some shit!
我看这车没法开了
This looks like a disabled vehicle to me.
你放心吧
Hey,don't worry about it.
我们会列个详细清单,包括你在后备箱的所有东西
We'll do a full inventory,including everything in the trunk.
我们可不想让你说警察偷了你的东西
Yeah,we wouldn't want you accusing the LAPD of stealing anything.
- 拜托!- 提供点线索,弗朗克
- Hey,come on,all right?Hey!- Give us something,Franco.
- 提供点线索吧 - 这真是胡闹!真是的!
- Give us something.- This here is bullshit!Come on,man!
弗朗克,你怎么办?
Come on,Franco,what do you wanna do?
你们两个人简直就是
You know,you two guys,you're a couple of...
- 把车吊起来!- 你在干什么?
- All right,hook it up!- What are you doing?
- 轻点,这可是新车!- 你在干什么?
- Come on!Be nice,it's a new car!- What are you doing?
好,好,我提供点情况
Okay,okay,okay,all right!I got something for you guys,all right?
- 什么情况?
- Come here.- What do you got?
有这么一些人,想更进一步
There's...They got these guys,they're trying to go upscale.
- 干一笔大的 - 什么?
- They're planning something big.- What?
肯定打算干笔大的
They're definitely planning something real big.
- 干什么?- 这我不知道
- Like what?- I don't know like what.
但我知道他们会用到C4炸药
But I know they're gonna use a C-4 on the job.
你好?
What's up?
你好
Sup.
你一个人来的?
You alone?
就像电话里说的那样
Like I said on the phone.
没带家伙
He's clean.
- 没有同伙 - 你就是保罗?
- No one.- You Paulie?
就像牌子上写的那样
Like the sign says.
你想买C4炸药?
So,you're the one who wants some C-4?
就像电话里说的那样
Like I said on the phone.
有人买了一大批 外面都缺货
I know,the street's gone dry.Someone bought up a big pile of it.
所以你就来找我了?
That what brings you to me?
- 聪明人
- Smart man.- Yeah.
让我看看你的一类许可证
So,let me see your category one permit.
许可证?我本以为很简单的
Permit?Thought this was supposed to be simple.
没错 只要你有许可证
It is.You got a permit.
我的一类证件
My category one.
是的,很简单
Yeah,it is simple.
我们收下钱,你什么都得不到
See,we take your money,and you don't get shit.
过来!
Get over here!
好了!好了
Hey,whoa!Hey.Come on.
你要是敢动 就在你的头上添几个洞
Move,I put three holes in your head like a bowling ball,big boy.
简简单单的多好?
Should've kept it simple,huh?
- 我们估计你需要帮忙 - 帮忙?
- Thought you might need some backup.- Backup?
你好像被揍得不轻
Looked like you getting your ass kicked.
我让你们在车里等着
Man,I told you guys to wait in the car.
- 你一个人能摆平啊?- 我确实摆平了
- You had it under control,huh?- Yeah,I did,actually.
- C4炸药呢?- 在库房里
- Where's the C-4?- It's in the shed.
- 老实说在哪儿?- 在库房里!
- Speak English!Where's the C-4?- It's in the shed!
- 在后面库房里!- 在库房里?
- Back in the shed!- In the shed?
- 在库房里吗?- 后面库房里
- It's in the shed?- Back in the shed.
在库房里
It's in the shed.
干得好 让弗朗克交代了
Nice job squeezing Franco.
不说,他就要坐十年牢了
Looking at 10 years,funny how he gave up that address.
你觉得他们就是FedCal银行的抢劫犯吗?
Think it's the FedCal guys?
会使用C4炸药的人没几个警长
Only so many people know how to use C-4,Chief.
- 邓肯!- 卡沃警官?
- Duncan!- Lieutenant Carver?
- 快走吧,杰克!- 我要和杰克警官谈谈!
- Moving and grooving,Jack!- I wanna speak to Detective Welles!
我现在没时间
I can't do this right now.
我们有搜查令
We're executing a search warrant.
属干警察 公干
Police work.Remember what that is?
要让内务部等着吗
Internal Affairs will have to wait.
你绐我打电话,威尔士 你要联系我!
Hey,you call me,Welles.Get back to me!
别逼我去找你!
You don't want me to have to come find you!
你怎么突然来这里?
The hell is wrong with you,coming down here now?
我让你看一段录像
I wanna show you something.
警察趴在地上!
Police,on the ground now!
上!
Go!
威尔士,我这里没人
Welles,I got nothing.
哈奇,他去了春天大街!
Hatch,he's coming up on Spring!
天!
Shit!
威尔士!
Welles!
- 你没事吧?- 没事
- You all right?- Yeah.
两个死者,伊森舍曼斯基和康斯坦丁舍曼斯基
Our two dead guys,Ethan and Constantine Symanski.
兄弟俩 俄国黑手党嫌疑人,但是和FedCal银行抢劫案无关
Brothers.Suspected Russian mob,but they're no good for the FedCal job.
- 为什么?- 移民局说抢劫案发生的时候
- Why's that?- INS said they were being sworn in
他们正宣誓成为美国公民
as U.S.Citizens at the time of the robbery.
- 原来是两个叛国者?- 是啊
- Couple patriots,huh?- Yeah.
我们到来之前他们烧了很多东西
They burned a bunch of stuff before we got here.
只剩下这个
This is all that was left.
像是洛杉矶地图
Looks like a map of LA.
可能
Yeah.Maybe.
看看这些东西 C4炸药自动步枪雷管
Look at this stuff.C-4,automatic weapons,blasting caps.
肯定是准备做大案
They were definitely onto something big.
斯台普斯中心,珀欣广场,联合车站
Staples Center,Pershing Square,Union Station.
他们想干什么?
The hell were they up to?
- 可以了 - 杰克连线好了 准备好了吗?
- We're good to go.- Jake's all connected.You ready?
我们准备好了,杰西
All right,Jesse,we're up.
演示一下
Show it to us.
好
Nice.
让杰克别再演示了
All right,tell Jake to stop showing off.
好了,关闭吧
All right,man,turn it off.
- 好样的 - 好样的
- Good job.- Good job.
但关键是还有3天了,到底能不能行?
But the point is,I mean,can we do it in three days?
不但能行,还能很安全
Not only can we do it,but we're gonna play it safe.
我们每小时钻一英寸,
All right,we're gonna drill at about an inch an hour,
16个洞要64小时
16 holes in 64 hours.
分开来干,按照进度
Split the work,keep the schedule.
这样准备时间就只有一天了?
So,that leaves us one last day for prep?
没错 足够我和杰克安装线路了
Exactly.Enough time for Jake and I to wire.It's good.
好,我给拉威打电话 看看今晚能不能到那里
All right,I'm gonna call Rahway and see if we can get down there tonight.
谁啊?
Who's there?
戈登!
G!
内奥米 你怎么来了?你不是在
Naomi.What are you doing here?You're supposed to be at the...
是啊,是啊
I know,I know,I...
- 我先走了 - 好
- Catch up with you later,man.- All right,man.
这里真好
Wow,look at this place.
这是怎么回事?内奥米?
What is this?Naomi?
我彻底戒毒了 感觉很好
Look,I am really clean now.I feel great.
内奥米,你说什么呢?
Naomi,what are you talking about?
再多呆一周也没什么用
Look,another week in that place wouldn't have made any difference.
- 我们不是说好了吗?- 行了
- We spoke about this,didn't we?- Come on.
我做的很好
I was doing really well.
问他们能不能提前走,他们同意了
I asked if I could leave early,and they said yes.
不信你打电话问问
If you don't believe me,call them.
他们说离开戒毒,所以后要有个生活目标
Look,they told us that when you get out,you got to have a plan.
没有生活目标是不行的
Yeah?Without a plan,you're dead.
于是我想到了你,我的目标,我们回老家
So I started thinking about you and me,our plan,and going home.
会实现的
And that's gonna happen.
但你还需要一周,只要一周
You had one more week,that's all,one more week.
我这几天很忙
It's a busy time for me,Naomi.
- 你不记得了吧?- 我不记得了
- You don't remember it,do you?- No,I don't.
看你当时多么可爱 妈妈真美
Look at how cute you were.Mum was so beautiful.
当时我很幸福
I was truly happy back then.
只有回老家我才算真正康复了,才能真正重新开始
I'm not gonna be right until I get back there,so I can start again.
能做到的 只需要3天
And we can.In just three days.
我在工作 我要送你去旅馆
I'm working.I need to put you in a hotel.
我住这里不行吗?
What?Why can't I stay here?
行 只是现在不合适
You can.It's just a bad time for me.
好吗?
All right?
好吧
Yeah.
我能看出不是街道地图
Well,I can tell you it's not a street map.
应该是某种市政工程图
It's some kind of a public works project.
没有参考数字的话 我也无法确定
But without a reference number,there's no way I can work it out.
好 谢谢
All right.Thanks.
不客气
You got it.
里弗斯,德朗特
Rivers,Delonte.
靠上去
Put your body in it.
接住,小艾迪 上篮
Right here,Eddie.Up with it.
漂亮!这样才对
Yes!That's what I'm talking about.
小艾迪 让着你叔叔,杰克
Hey,Eddie.Take it easy on Uncle Jack,all right?
暂停 我昨晚调查了一下 想和你谈谈
Time out.I did some work last night.Wanted to talk to you.
你要呕吐的话吐到草地上
Hey,if you're gonna puke,do it on the grass.
爸爸,让我们打完吧
Come on,Dad,let us finish.
你来替换我吧?
Yeah,why don't you take my place?
不用了 你接着打球吧,小艾迪
I'm good.Go ahead,keep playing,Eddie.
- 小艾迪的情况好多了 - 好得很
- Eddie looks like he's doing a lot better.- Yeah,he's doing great,man.
他上次透析有一个月了
I mean,it's been about a month since his last dialysis.
几天内还不行,然后渐渐康复
Down for a couple days,then he bounces back.I mean...
- 你发现了什么情况?
- So,anyway,what's up?- All right.
你记得几年前韩国居民区的 珠宝抢劫案吗?
You remember the jewelry job in Koreatown,few years back?
劫匪利用电线从一栋楼 逃到另一栋楼?
They used wires and went from one building to the other?
一个警卫抓住了其中一个劫匪
Guard got loose.He ended up shooting one of them?
记得那个警卫后来成了大英雄
Yeah.The guard ended up being like a big hero.
那个在楼梯中弹的劫匪?
The perp got shot on a fire escape,right?
叫德朗特里弗斯,绰号老鬼
Name's Delonte Rivers,a.k.a.Ghost.
刚在Chino监狱服刑5年
He just finished serving five at Chino.
他在监狱中的证件 不知怎么到了俄国人手里
And somehow,his prison ID ended up at the Russians.
我在照片上看到的
I saw it in the Polaroids.
你是说这个人参与了银行抢劫案?
So,you think this guy's good for the FedCal heist?
不知道 他在银行抢劫案的当天被释放
I don't know.He was released the same day the bank was hit.
肯定不只是巧合
There's got to be some type of connection there,right?
麦克斯 什么事?
Yeah,Max.What's up?
- 早上好,杰克 - 你好,莫妮卡
- Morning,Jack.- Hey,Monica.
慢点说
Whoa,whoa,slow down.
- 营销代表 - 开什么玩笑
- Marketing rep.- You got to be kidding me.
麦克斯,你让卡沃周一给我打电话
Look,Max,you can just tell Carver he can call me Monday.
我周末不上班
I don't work weekends,okay?
内务部找我
Internal Affairs.
我为你做早饭吧?
Well,can I make you some breakfast,Jack?
不了 我要去接桑迪 我们要去参观几处名胜
No,that's all right.I got to pick Sunday up.We're gonna go look at some landmarks.
- 周一再见 - 再见,杰克
- I'll see you Monday.- See you,Jack.
今天的作业是去哪里?
So,what do we got?What's the assignment for today?
先去星光大道,然后写一篇参观感受
After we go to the Walk of Fame,I'm supposed to write about us going there.
孩子,星光大道算不上名胜,名不符实
Honey,the Walk of Fame's not a landmark,it's a tourist trap.
我知道个更好的名胜 我们去拉布里沥青坑,
I got a better landmark.Let's go over to La Brea Tar Pits,
然后再去博物馆,
and then afterwards we can go to the museum,
去看看化石
we can look at the fossils.
然后再去“农贸市场”吃汉堡
And then after that,we can go to the Farmer's Market and get some burgers.
好主意 我们去“农贸市场”吃汉堡 喝奶昔
Good idea.Burgers and shakes at the Farmer's Market.
你有什么情况?
Yeah,what do you got for me?
孩子,我们要先停下车
Sweetheart,we're gonna have to make a stop somewhere first.
我昨晚接到你的电话以后,调查了里弗斯的档案,
When I got your message from last night,I pulled Rivers' file,
他今天下午有个假释会面
saw he was due this afternoon.
他这样的罪犯 提前释放还要安排几次会面
Cons like him,they're good for a visit or two.
不过四年的一级监禁,我看会面也没用
But four years of lockdown,I wouldn't bet on him.
就是他 要不要我拦住他问问?
There's your boy now.Want me to hold him?Rattle his cage?
不,还是按常规来吧
No.No,keep it routine.
- 你知道他的住址吗?- 住在长滩的某个破地方
- You got an address on this guy?- Some dump in Long Beach.
应该住一周左右
Probably good for a week,if that.
好,谢谢
All right,thanks.
去小东京
Little Tokyo.Let's go.
现在能去博物馆了吗?
Now are we going to the museum?
一会就去
Just a sec,honey.We will.
- 还要别的吗?- 这个要两包
- Anything else?- Give me a couple of these,too.
右边
Here,on the right.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks,man.- You got it.
- 你好?- 你来晚了
- What's up?- You're late.
- 会面进行的怎么样?- 挺好
- How'd the parole meeting go?- We good.
屁大的事还要弄的这么麻烦
You know they try and turn pissing in a cup into a seven-game series.
不过没事了
We straight,though.
- 你要买什么?- 带酱热狗
- Can I help you?- Relish.
- 杰西 - 你好?
- Jesse.- What's up?
怎么了?其他人呢?
What's happening?Where the guys?
我出来买吃的 他们都等着我
I'm take-out.They're waiting on me.
好的
Sounds good.
- 拿到了吗?- 我办事你还不放心
- So,did you get it?- Come on,man.It's me.
爸爸你看什么呢?
What are you looking at,Daddy?
一会就好
Just a second,honey.
和救援队用的一样
Same thing the rescue workers use.
操作很简单
Easy as shit.Works just like a can opener.
- 和调度员谈过了吗?- 谈过了
- Speak to the dispatcher?- Yeah.
谈过了,今天早上和他联系的 放心吧
Yeah,yeah,yeah,I spoke to him this morning.We good.
- 说实话 - 路线是确定的
- Come on,man.- Hey,the route's a lock,G.
再见
Talk to you later.
你还是担心别人吧,戈登
Hey,man,find you something else to worry about,G.
别担心我
I got you,homes.
什么?
What?
坐稳了,孩子
Hold on to your seat,honey.
会不会开车啊?
What are you doing,idiot?
你找找有笔吗?没有?
You see a pen,baby?No?
看见那辆蓝色轿车了吗?隔着两辆车?
There,you see that blue sedan back there?Two cars back?
- 看见了 - 他在跟踪我们
- Yeah.- He's sharking us.
右拐
Make a right.
你有笔吗?
You have a pen,baby?Anything?
再右拐
All right,make another right.
- 他跟定我们了 - 对
- He's staying with us.- Yeah.
我们停车
Let's pull over.
- 他们是什么人?- 不算什么人
- Who are they?- They're just some guys.
- 是警察吗?- 不可能带着孩子
- Is it a cop?- With a kid?
你急着叫我来有什么要紧事?
What's so important that you'd drag my ass all the way down here?
- 我找到他了 - 谁?
- I found him,Hatch.- Who?
银行抢劫案的劫匪戈登科泽 看看这家伙
Him,FedCal.Gordon Cozier.I mean,look at that.
身高,体型,样样符合
Same height,same build,same everything.
先等等 你说什么?
Wait,hold on.What are you talking about?
- 你怎么得出这一结论?- 里弗斯去参加假释会面,
- Where's all this coming from?- I followed that guy,Rivers,
然后我跟踪了他
from his parole meeting.
- 他在商业区下了出租车 - 带着孩子跟踪?
- And he gets out of a cab downtown.- With Sunday?
你在竞选“年度最佳父亲”吗?
What,are you gunning for Father of the Year now?
我在车上,看见他去了一个热狗摊
And from my car,I see him go to this hot-dog stand.
科泽也在 里弗斯背对着我
And Cozier's there.Now,he's got his back to me.
但我肯定他给了科泽什么东西
But I swear I see Rivers pass something to him.
过了一会一个骑摩托车的
A second later,this guy on a motorcycle,he looks at Cozier.
在离开以前看了科泽一眼,
And then right before he takes off,bam,
和银行劫匪是同一个手势
the same gesture the asshole used in the bank.
然后我跟踪科泽 抄下了他的车牌号
And then I followed Cozier and got his license plate number.
看你画的 用蜡笔写的?
Yeah,it's very official.What is that,crayon?
我肯定就是他
Look,man,I'm telling you,it's him.
可你看不见他的脸 就没有证据
Except you can't see his face.The guy's got a clean sheet.
他只是个有前科的人
Come on,man,you follow an ex-con
也没参加银行抢劫,你还跟踪他到热狗摊?
who's no good for the bank job to,what,a hot-dog stand?
- 然后他和某人见面
- Then he meets somebody...- Listen to me.
也许见了面,也许没见面
Maybe he meets somebody there,maybe he doesn't.
- 也许他递给他什么东西 - 听着,我告诉你我当时在那儿
- Maybe he passes something...- Look,Hatch,I'm telling you I was there.
买了一个带酱热狗,
...and buys a hot-dog with ketchup and relish,
- 然后一个骑托车的
- and then,some guy on a motorcycle says...- Call me crazy.
"告别," 然后走人了
"So long," and rides off.
就凭这些你能证明什么呢?
Come on,man,give a brother a break.Are you kidding me?
我们还能去“农贸市场”吗?
Can we still go to the Farmer's Market,Daddy?
孩子,对不起 天
Baby,I'm sorry.Geez.
没想到这么晚了 我们可以去别的地方吃饭
I can't believe it's this late.We can go eat somewhere else.
只要再过一会 你想去哪儿都可以
Just gonna take a few minutes here.Wherever you want.
真是的
Shit.
你知道你爸爸很爱你吧?
Your daddy loves you very much,you know that,right?
- 别忘了这一点?- 好的
- Don't ever forget that,okay?- Okay.
你要有可靠的证据,杰克
Take care of the real stuff,Jack.
我们吃比萨,如何?
Hey,how about some pizza,huh?
我只想回家
I just wanna go home.
走吧
Let's go.
什么时候的事?
Well,when'd it happen?
没事 没事 如果她想回来你帮个忙,
No,no,no.It's all right.If she comes back,do me a favor,
尽量把她留住,吉姆,再给我打电话
you just keep her there,all right,Jimmy,and you call me.
不能让她离开旅馆 知道吗?
She doesn't leave the hotel.Do you understand me?
好
All right.
内奥米?
Naomi?
我在旅馆给吉米留了些钱 他没放进保险柜
I left Jimmy some money at the hotel.He didn't put it in the safe.
- 她把钱拿走了?- 她拿着钱走了 真是的!
- She took it?- She's gone and so is the money.Shit!
- 你干什么?- 我要停车
- What you doing,mate?- I'm pulling over.
- 为什么?- 因为你想去找她
- Why?- 'Cause you got to find her.
今晚隧道的活我替你
I'll take your time in the tunnel tonight.
- 谢谢了 - 客气什么
- Thanks.- You got it.
真是的
Damn it.
- 上面舒服吗?- 得了吧
- How's it hanging?- Funny guy.
好,下来吧
All right,come on down.
我们明早大干一场
We'll go hot tomorrow morning.
会惊天动地的
This is gonna be lovely.
嗨,戈登
Hey,G.
准备好了?
We good?
一切都好
All signs point to it.
- 有内奥米的消息吗?- 没有
- Any word from Naomi?- No.
我觉得她这次真的走了
This time,I think she's gone.
她不会有事的
She'll turn up fine.
你为何这么肯定?
What makes you so sure?
你是她唯一的亲人,不会抛下你的
If I had any family left,that's where I'd be.
如果明天有什么差错 我们不能让他跑了
You know,if anything goes wrong tomorrow,we can't let him walk away.
他还能把04年的事供出去
He could still hang us for '04.
我可以动手
I'll bring the insurance.
你来了 你好吗,老鬼?
There he is.How's it going,Ghost?
好得很
I can't call it,gentlemen.
- 你们好吗?
- Yeah.- What's happening?
- 戈登 - 好啊
- G.Cool.- Yeah,man.
又能干一笔了 感觉真好就像回到了从前啊
Feels good to be back in action again.It's like old times,huh?
事成之后我们在哪儿会面?
So,where we meeting at after the drop?
斯考特正在确定 我明天会告诉你
Scott's giving me the information.I'll let you know tomorrow.
“来尝尝毁灭的滋味”
"Come sip from the cup of destruction."
- 成吉思汗的话 - 对 我崇拜的人之一
- Genghis Khan.- Yeah.One of my heroes.
想得到什么,他就会去夺取
Saw what he wanted,reached out and took it.
我们明天要做的事也一样
Like us,tomorrow.
我们也一样
Just like us.
- 为了明天 - 为了明天
- To tomorrow.- To tomorrow.
为了明天
To tomorrow.
喂?
Yeah?
慢点说 什么?你在哪儿?
Slow down,slow down.What?Where are you?
好的 我这就去
All right.Wait,no,no,I'm coming.I'm coming.
办公室在哪儿?
Where do I find Processing?
进去那个门 沿着黄线就到
Through the far door.Follow the yellow line.
副警长办公室在哪儿?
Where's Vice?
下楼去地下室
Take the stairs to the basement.
我们上周收到银行钞票清单的传真,
We got your fax last week about the bank bills,
查到这混蛋手上有不少百元大钞,
so when we nailed this scum with a bunch of fresh hundreds,
就给你们打了电话
thought we'd call you.
这个混蛋?不会吧
This low-life?You gotta be kidding me.
他和女友卖毒品的时候被我们抓住了
He was hustling some stolen shit with his girlfriend when we stopped him.
钞票都没做记号,但我们估计是抢的钱
None of the bills were marked,but we figure they gotta be from some job.
你审问他了吗?
Did you question him?
没有 他情绪不稳
No.He didn't go easy.
也抽了很多毒品 我们想等他先平静一下
He's high as hell,too.We decided to let him chill.
好 我和他谈谈
All right.Let me talk to this guy.
我没功夫看你演戏 你的钞票哪儿来的?
All right,I don't have time for this bullshit.Where did you get the bills?
不用帮忙!
I got him!
再问你一遍 你的钞票哪儿来的?
I'm not gonna ask you again.Where did you get the bills?
- 是贷款的钱!- 胡说!
- It was a loan,man,it was a loan!- A loan.Bullshit!
说是谁 谁给的
I want a name.Give me a name.
- 内奥米 - 内奥米什么?
- Naomi.- Naomi what?
- 内奥米什么啊?她姓什么?- 不知道!我刚认识她
- Naomi what?She got a last name?- I don't know,man!I just met her.
也调查过她了吗?
You bust her,too?
对,她叫内奥米科泽
Yeah,her name's Naomi Cozier.
科泽?你听见了吗,哈奇?
Cozier?Did you hear that,Hatch?
听见了
Yeah.
我可不愿回旅馆 一个人干坐着
I ain't going back to no hotel to sit on my own.
你不去旅馆,
Right,you ain't going back to the hotel,
也不去什么加勒比海
you ain't going to the freaking Caribbean either.
你要回戒毒所继续戒毒
You're going back to the rehab to start your program again.
- 我不去!- 非去不可!
- Hell,no,I ain't!- Yes,you are!
我受够了医生和护士当着我的面
I'm tired of them nurses and doctors making you stand up
和陌生人谈论我的情况
and chat your business in front of strangers.
你每次都这样,每次都是出来两天又去吸毒了!
Every time,you do the same thing!Every time!Two days out of rehab!
刚出来两天又进警察局了
Just two days and you're in the police station already.
我给你的钱呢?都买毒品了吧?
Where's the money I gave you?Is it in your veins?
你少管我的事
You know,your problem is you're too into my shit.
因为你不在乎自己!
Let me see your arm.Your shit.You're not into your own shit!
你管你自己的事吧?你根本不在乎我
Why don't you get a life?You don't care about me.
都不让我住在你那里
You wouldn't even let me stay at your apartment.
- 嫌我丢你的人 还是我把你养活大的!
- That's right.- You're ashamed of me.And I raised you!
整天吸毒的人还养活我?
You raised me?My crackhead sister raised me?
- 你连自己都养活不了 - 忘恩负义的混蛋!
- Can't even raise yourself.- You ungrateful bastard!
- 别说了 - 你算什么
- Shut up.- But you ain't worth shit,man.
- 当初把你送人就好了!- 你说得对
- I should've let Welfare take you!- You're right,you're right.
我真糊涂
Wonder.
内奥米!
Naomi!
别走!内奥米!
No!Naomi!Naomi!
戈登科泽 20分钟前把她领走了
Gordon Cozier.Signed for her 20 minutes ago.
- 两天内第二次听到这个名字了 - 是啊
- Second time in two days.- Yeah,I hear you.
即使这钱证明是抢的,也不能证明是科泽干的
Even if we tie those bills to a certain job,it doesn't prove Cozier did anything.
现在提审他的话,只怕会打草惊蛇让他跑了
Question him now,he lawyers up,splits town.We can blow this case.
只要能证明抢劫案当天他进了电梯,
If we can put him in the elevators on the day of the heist,
就有了足够的证据
we'll have plenty to talk to him about.
到时间了 别再谈情说爱了
It's time.Let's go,Casanova.
今晚再见
I'll see you tonight.
你小心
You be careful.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you.- Love you,too.
快点,情圣!走吧!
Come on,lover boy!Let's go,mate!
还有正事呢 来吧
Got a job to do,baby.Come on.
我们走!
Let's go,let's go!
喝咖啡吗?还是吃点心?
You want a coffee?Donut?Anything?
不用
Naw.I'm okay.
杰克 卡沃找你
Hey,Jack.Carver wants to see you.
现在没空 FedCal银行抢劫案就要破了
Not now,Max.We're getting close on this FedCal job.
这不是请求你,杰克
It's not a request,Detective Welles.
这是命令
Orders,Jack.
好吧
All right.
你们太软弱了,警长
This is chicken shit,Chief.
海地人,俄罗斯人 很多时候我都需要当机立断
The Haitian,the Russians.I make judgment calls every day.
- 我也有权找个律师,
- The union says I get an attorney...- Before you go on about this,
- 就像被我揍的混蛋一样
- you need to......just like the assholes
- 杰克别说了!
- I gotta deal with out there.- Jack,stop!
5分钟后如果你还想找律师 可以给你
Look,if you still want to see a lawyer in five minutes,you can have one.
先坐下
Sit down.
趴下!趴在地上!
Get down!Get on the ground!Get on the ground!Spread your legs!
- 趴在地上- 这是你们突击海地人,
- Keep your head down.- The day you busted the Haitian,
禁毒处在街道对面安装有摄像头
Narcotics had surveillance set up in the building across the street.
- 闭嘴!- 我说过他们会给你钱!
- Shut up!Stay down!- I said they'd give you money!
- 什么钱?- 就是这里的钱!
- What?What money?- Money,right there!
在那儿,别动!好了你走吧
Stay there,don't move!All right.All right,get out of here.Go.
关了 关了吧
Turn it off.All right,turn it off.
我想让你知道你的搭档是什么人
I wanted you to know who you were working with.
我觉得应该先告诉你
Felt I owed you that much.
内务部要提起指控 今天就在准备材料
Internal Affairs is bringing charges.Papers are being drawn up today.
你要送哈奇回家的话我能理解
You wanna drop Hatcher?I understand.
怎么会这样
No,no.No.No.
谈的怎么样?
How'd it go?
还是老一套
You know,same old,same old.
对毒品贩子也不让动粗
Shouldn't have roughed up that drug dealer,you know?
- 就这点事?- 对
- That's the beef?That's it?- Yeah.
给我记个警告
Warning,short and sweet.
你看看 就是他
Check it out.That's our guy.We got him.
该锁定科泽先生了 我们去找他吧
Time to turn up the heat on Mr.Cozier.Let's go pay him a visit.
一切就绪 准备开工吧
All right,we're hot.Ready to rock,man.
好 关闭信号灯
All right.Kill the traffic light.
开始了
Let's go.
执勤交警
Officer on duty.
好,警官 运钞车5分钟后到
All right,Officer.Package is due in five minutes.
岗哨监视他
Crow's nest.Put an eye on him.
收到
Copy that.
你来开车
You're driving.
提提精神吧!
Come on,let's go!
你到底怎么了?
Come on,man.What's wrong with you?
你为何这么做,艾迪?
Why'd you do it,Eddie?
为何拿走那笔钱?
Why'd you take the money?
我不明白你的意思?
What are you...What are you talking about?
都录下来了
They got it on tape.
你为何这么做?
Why'd you do it?
唉
Shit,man.
莫妮卡下岗了 还要偿还房贷 保险金那么少
Monica's laid off.We got a mortgage.Insurance doesn't pay shit.
还有孩子的医疗费
All these medical bills.
你一定要帮帮我,杰克
You gotta help me,Jack.
钱摆在我面前 我就忍不住拿了
It was right there.It was right there,and I took it.
有困难怎么不找我?
Why didn't you come to me?
我是小艾迪的教父呢
I'm Eddie's godfather.
你我情同手足
Come on.You're like my brother.
可我需要的钱不是小数,一辈子都挣不来
The kind of money I'm talking about,you couldn't save it in a lifetime.
六年来你一直照顾我
Look,you've had my back for the last six years.
我自然会尽全力帮你,知道吗?
I'm gonna do whatever it takes to help you,okay?
好
Yeah.
运钞车还没有来
Package is late.
肯定有事耽搁了 会来的 真是的!老是烦我
Must've gotten hung up.They'll be here.Goddamn!Get off my ass.
肯定有问题 肯定有问题
This is not good.This is not good.
要下手就说一声,戈登,我准备好了
Let me know,G.I'm ready.
你们要有信心
Come on,boys,have some faith.
我一直都信不过他 我们得做些什么
I never trusted this guy.This is bad,we gotta do something.
在洛杉矶迟到很正常
This is LA,man.Nothing runs on time.
我们这里一大堆C4炸药,弄不好命都没了
Damn all that.We got a shitload of C-4,and we're live down here.Come on.
冷静
Just be cool,all right?
运钞车到底在哪儿?老鬼,告诉我?
Where the hell is it,Ghost?Talk to me.Where is it?
真是的,肯定会来的
They're coming,God damn it.They'll be here.
只要你下令,我就开枪
Say the word,G.I'll send it.
肯定会来的 你们急什么真是的!
Y'all need to relax.I told you they coming.Damn!
戈登,我们不能坐以待毙
G,we gotta make a move.Come on,man.
别说了!
All right!
你在哪儿,约翰?
Where you at,John?
我知道你肯定在楼顶,混蛋
I know you up there,son of a bitch.
有什么情况吗?
Well?Is there anDhing?
没有 如果他要逃跑, 这是最后干掉他的机会
Nada.If he bolts,this may be our last shot,right now.
- 戈登 - 大家都别急
- G.- Everybody,stay sharp.
肯会来的只是晚了一点而已
They'll be here,G.Theyjust running a little behind.
我们不能干等着了
We gotta do something.Come on.
快,怎么还不来?
Come on,bitch.Where are you?
干掉他
Take him out.
来了!来了!我就说过会来!
They're here!They're here,God damn it!I told you they were coming!
好了,等等,等等!
All right,hold up,hold up!
都准备好!
Buckle up,boys!
现在下了坡道
They're turning down the ramp now.
火车要离站了
Train's about to leave the station.
戈登,他们来了
A'ight,G.Here they come.
正前往第四大道
Merging onto 4th.
该死的 不会吧?
God damn it.You kidding me?
怎么停下了?
What's the holdup?
我正拦住交通 给个话啊
Come on,guys,I'm holding traffic.Just give me the word.
目标区域还有汽车
All right,boys,we've still got cars inside the cones here.
好,保持联系
All right,keep me posted.
快啊
Come on.
快点啊!怎么了?
Come on,already!Yo,what's up?
- 让我们走吧!- 你还让不让人走啊?
- Let's go!- You gonna move this or what?
我看目标区域没车了 给我个话
Cones look clear to me.Holla at me.
让他们通过吧,警官
Go on ahead and wave them through,Officer.
总算让走了!
Finally!
会不会开车啊?
Where you going?
开始行动了!
Showtime,boys!
- 好了 - 好,行动
- All right,it's on.- All right,here we go.
- 开始吧!- 现在看你们的了!
- It's on!- It's in your hands now!
我们挣钱吧!
Let's get paid,man!
50码!
Fifty yards!
25码!10码!
Twenty-five yards!Ten yards!
- 骑车的小心!- 引爆!
- Look out!Bike!- Hit it!
该死的!骑自行车的!
Holy shit!Goddamn bicyclist!
该死!
Shit!
- 你怎么样?
- Jesus Christ!- You all right?
该死的,提前了一点点!
Damn it,too soon!
运钞车还在路面上!
I still see the trucks!
没炸到运钞车呢?
We missed!Where is it?
- 紧急刹车了 - 怎么回事?
- Truck stopped short.- What's going on?
- 真是的,杰克,爆炸太早了
- Shit!- God damn it,Jake,you went too early.
你就闭嘴吧,老鬼!
Shut up,Ghost,shut up!
街道发生爆炸!我们遇险了 快离开!
The street blew up!We're in trouble.We gotta get out of here!
呆在车里!我俩去接应!
Stay in that truck!We'll get you out of this!
- 下车疏导交通!- 戈登,现在怎么办?
- Get out and move that traffic,let's go!- G,now what?
- 我们怎么办?- 岗哨!你在哪儿,岗哨?
- What we doing?- Crow's nest!Where are you,crow's nest?
- 杰克,计划流产,我们必须走
- Talk to me,talk to me!- Jake,it's a bust,man.
- 我们必须走人!
- We gotta get out of here!- What are we doing,G?
- 我什么都看不见!- 按计划!呆在!
- I can't see shit!- Follow procedure!Stay in that truck!
- 我们走吧!
- Okay,let's clear this!- G,call it off!
- 都别说了
- No,no,hold on!- What are y'all doing?
戈登!
G!
取消行动!取消行动!
Abort!Abort!
一切都乱套了!
All hell broke loose up here,man!
戈登!
G!
快走!这次行动取消!
Let's go,let's go!We gotta abort this,we gotta abort this!
- 等等!我看见有情况!
- Abort,abort!- Hold on,hold on!I see something up here!
有人在行动
We got a man on the move.
不行,我们马上取消行动!
No,Officer,we're aborting this now!
先别急,有人在行动!
Not yet,God damn it,we got action!
我在上面看得更清楚,戈登!先拖住他们!
You don't see what I see,G!Just keep them busy!
这个疯子要干什么?
What's this crazy son of a bitch doing?
喂!
Hey!
天!他打倒了一个警卫!
Shit!He just jacked a guard!
开门!
Open this door!
他占领了一辆车!
We got a vehicular,people!
他上了车!
He in the truck!
这个疯子干起来了!
Crazy son of a bitch is going for it!
他撞车了!
He hit the car!
下面腾出地方!
Keep it clear down below,boys!
- 天,他要来了!- 他来了,他来了!
- Shit,man,here he come!- Here he comes,here he comes!
他撞了前面的车!
He's ramming the truck!
- 车来了!- 让开!
- Here it come!- Get out of the way!
这样才对,漂亮!
That's what I'm talking about!Damn!
- 拿工具!- 火力掩护!
- Get the jaws,get the jaws!- Keep them back!
混蛋!
Shit!Little bastard!
这家伙真是胆大包天!
Soldier boy done lost his damn mind!
天!他要干什么?
Shit!What's he doing?
他遇到麻烦了
Our man got a problem here.
撞向警卫!
Hit the guard!
下面小心!
Incoming!
好啊
Hell,yeah.
去接他!
Take his shit!
有我呢来
I've got you,man.Come on.Got you.
成功了
We got it.
都注意运钞车抢劫案,第四大道和撖榄街路口
All units,211 on an armored vehicle,4th and Olive.
重复,运钞车抢劫案第四大道和橄榄街路口
Repeat,armored vehicle robberyin progress,4th and Olive.
第四大道和橄榄街路口 是他们
4th and Olive.That's them.
掉头
Turn the car around.
我送你回家
I'm taking you home,Eddie.
掉头吧 离这里很近
Come on,turn the car around.It's a couple blocks away.
- 不行 - 真是的,我还没撤职呢!
- No,man.- God damn it,man,I'm still a cop!
快掉头!
Turn the car around!
好吧
All right.
我们快点!
Let's hustle,boys,come on!
耶!
Yeah!
- 快走,杰克!
- Come on!- Come on,Jake!
走,走!
Go,go,go,go!
我们走!
Yeah,let's go,let's go,let's go,let's go!
快走!
Move it,move it!
看
Look at this.
这可需要很多炸药
Took a shitload of explosives to do this.
- C-4炸药 - 对
- C-4.- Yeah.
- 有什么情况?- 两辆车掉在洞里
- What do you got?- We got two down in the hole.
警卫看见了其中一个人
Guard got a look at one of them.
30多岁的白人男性
Caucasian male,adult,in his 30s.
画像师正赶来
I got a sketch artist coming here now to work with our witness.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
他们早就走了!下水道四通八达
They're long gone!Sewer tunnels in every direction.
下水道?
Sewer tunnels?
记得我们在俄国人的窝点 发现的市政工程图吗?
Remember that public works map we found at the Russian safe house?
被烧毁的纸片?下水道,炸药 高性能武器
The burnt fragment?The sewers,explosives.High-powered weapons.
他们仍然抢劫了?
So the job went down without our two dead guys?
是的,你记得俄国人那里有张地铁地图吗？
Yeah,well,you remember the map?There was a subway map at the Russians.
你觉得下水道通往地铁站?
Yeah,you think the sewers connect to the subway station?
有可能,我们去看看
Could be,let's check it out.
- 最近的地铁站是哪里?- 珀欣广场
- What was the closest station circled?- Pershing Square.
借过
Pardon me.
就是他!戴灰帽子的!就在热狗摊上出现过!
That's him,Hatch!The guy with the gray hat!From the hot-dog stand!
- 糟糕!- 不许动!
- Shit!- Freeze!
- 看见一个逃跑的!- 别跑!
- We have a runner!- Stop!
混蛋!
Asshole!
让开,让开!
Get out the way,get out the way!
当心!当心!
Look out!Look out!
- 你疯了吗?
- Are you crazy?- Shit!
没伤着吧?喂!你跑什么?
You all right?Hey!Where you going,pal?
我们在追逐逃犯!
We're in pursuit!
前往珀欣广场
Headed toward Pershing Square.
他跑过停车场!
He's headed through the park!
让开 让开
Move.Move.Move.
别碰我的车!
Get off my car!Hey!
他离开了Grand!正前往图书馆!
He just left Grand!He's headed towards the library!
糟糕!
Shit!
警察!不许动!
Police!Freeze!
让开!
Move!
让开!让开!
Move,move,move,move!Get out the way!
警察!当心!
Police!Watch out!
- 他去哪儿了?- 那儿
- Which way did he go?- Back there.
- 这里有出口吗?- 没有
- Can we exit this way?- No.
- 让开!- 守住这几个门!
- Get out of the way!- Cover those doors!
- 走,走!- 他去了这个方向
- Move,move,move!- He went that way.
- 他去了那里 - 去了大厅
- He went that way.- Down the hall.
喂!
Hey!
让开!
Move it!
喂!
Hey,hey!
让开!让开!
Get out of my way!Get out of my way!
都出去!
Everybody,out!
振作,杰西
Come on,Jesse.
哈奇?
Hatch?
哈奇!
Hatch!
天啊!
Shit!
挺住,哥们 挺住 天啊
Hold on,buddy.Just hold on.Jesus.
- 这混蛋身手快 - 我是14组
- The son of a bitch was fast.- This is unit 14.
有警员受伤 门罗大楼六楼
I got an officer down.Sixth floor,Monroe building.
马上来救援
I need immediate assistance.
不许动!
Freeze!
他出去了!
He's outside!
挺住 尽力呼吸,哥们
Come on,come on.Just keep breathing,buddy.
尽力呼吸 坚持住
Keep breathing.Come on,stay with me.
快来救护人员!快!
I need that crash unit fast!Now!
哥们,坚持住
Come on,buddy.Hang in there.
让他跑了!
We lost him!
我这是因公殉职 因公殉职
Line of duty,Jack.Line of duty.
别乱想 你尽力呼吸
Yeah,come on.Come on.You just keep breathing.
你一定要坚持住 看着我
You gotta make it,man.Come on.Look at me,look at me.
我的家人,莫妮卡 你照顾小艾迪
My family,man.Monica.You take care of Eddie.
我会照顾你家人
I'm gonna take care of your family.Don't worry about that.
你放心 尽力呼吸
They're gonna be taken care of.You just keep breathing.
- 挺住 - 告诉莫妮卡我爱她
- Come on.- Tell Monica I love her.
- 我会的 - 说我爱她
- I will.- Tell her I love her.
挺住,哥们 坚持住
Come on,buddy.Hang in there.
是我
It's me.
我知道你是谁 我看了新闻 你当我是傻子吗?
I know who it is.I watch news.You think I'm stupid,you punk bitch?
别上火啊 你何必这么生气呢
Hey,cool it,brother.I sense a little too much hostility.
我只是为了大家
I was just trying to make everybody...
我把调度员给了你,你却找别人干了!
I give you dispatcher,and you do job with somebody else!
我死了两个手下 我要杀了你!
Two of my men dead.I kill you!
不会的 如果我死了,怎么给你一半的钱呢?
You do not wanna kill me.If I'm dead,how am I gonna get you half the money?
你还想要钱吧?
You do want the money,don't you?
现在消气了吧?我就知道
You listening now?Thought so.
我们在罗斯福酒店见面 我会说服他们给你一半
Hey,we meeting at the Roosevelt Hotel.I'm gonna convince them to give you half.
等会我告诉你房间号
I'll call you later with the room number.
我们都很难过,杰克 我刚和他妻子联系了
We're all real sorry,Jack.I just spoke with his wife.
监控录像的事怎么办?考虑一下他的家人?
What about the surveillance tape?His family?
还管什么录像啊 他因公殉职
Forget the tape.He was killed in the line of duty.
会为他举行正式葬礼,全额抚恤金
He'll get a cop's burial and full benefits.
那就好 谢谢
Good.Thanks.
你们在FedCal银行抢劫案上有了突破 是同一伙人吗?
You were making headway with FedCal Bank.Was it them?
不知道 我们看见有人跑就追上去了
I don't know.Guy started running,we chased him.
艾迪中枪 我也没抓住他
Eddie got shot.I got nothing.
你不要紧吧,杰克?
You okay,Jack?
我没事
Yeah.I'm fine.
- 杰克?有杰西的消息吗?- 没有
- Jake?You heard from Jesse?- No,not yet.
目前是1930万美元 轻松抢到最大的一笔
$19.3 million,so far.Easily the biggest lick yet,gentlemen.
目击者称
Witnesses report...
只怕他出事了
I can feel it,man.Something's not right.
都怪我 我不该让他参加的
This is my fault,man.I should've never brought him in.
- 老鬼?- 什么?
- Hey,Ghost?- Yes,sir?
好
Yeah.
这是04年抢劫案储蓄卡
That's the account card for the '04 job.
这是给俄国人的25万
That's $250,000 for the Russians.
我们的帐清了,老鬼
That puts us even now,Ghost.
你说什么,拉威?
Say what,Rahway?
你听见了 我们的帐清了
You heard me.That puts us even.
是啊 我的计划,你的指挥
Yeah,a'ight.My plan,your command.
我就知道你们靠得住
I knew I could trust y'all.
是谁?
Who is it?
是他 你去哪儿了?我一直给你打电话!
It's him.Where you been?I been calling you!
- 警察追我 - 警察?在哪儿?
- Police chased me.- Police?Where?
你把他们引来了?杰西?
You brought them here?Jesse,you brought them here?
没 我打中了一个
No.I shot one of them.
- 什么?- 什么?
- What?- What?
- 别说话!你开枪打了警察?- 我没办法
- Hold on!You shot a cop?- I had to,man.
- 钱呢?- 藏起来了
- Where the money?- I stashed it.
- 你把钱留下了!
- You left the money?Damn!- Goddamn!
都别说话!什么情况,跟我说说
Stashed it?Hold,hold on!Everyone,hold on.What happened,Jesse?Talk to me.
在地铁站,有两个警察
At the subway station,there was two cops.
然后他们就追我
And they just started chasing me.
地铁那么多人 为什么就追你呢?
And they chased you out the crowd because of what?
我怎么知道?
How,how the hell am I supposed to know?
- 为什么?- 老鬼 别说了
- Why?- Ghost.Hold on.
- 别说了!
- Hold on!Hold on!- No,man,let him tell me why!
- 我哪知道为什么!
- So,what happened?You shot because?- I don't know!
- 你为何对他开枪?
- I had to.He had me...- Why'd you shoot him?
因为你是笨蛋
'Cause you stupid.
没办法!他把我堵住
I had no choice!He had me.He had me cold,man.
可他没开枪 感觉就像
But he never fired at me.It was...It was kind of like...
像什么?
Like what?
好像他希望我开枪
Like he wanted me to shoot him.
笨蛋!
Stupid ass!
我揍死你
Shit!I'll beat the shit out of you.
- 放开他!
- G!G!Wait!- Let him go!Let him go!
你别拉我!走开!
Get off me!Yo,cool it.Get your hands off me!
- 你知道你做了什么吗?
- Back off!Back off!- You understand what you just did?
- 这不怪我!- 决不能对警察开枪!
- It wasn't my fault!- You don't shoot cops!
我自会处理!放开他!
I'll deal with it!Let him go!
那你去处理吧,杰克!
You deal with it then,Jake!
这可是死刑的罪名,年轻人,我不会陪你的
That's a death sentence,young blood,and I ain't going with you.
你真行,杰西
Nice one,Jesse.
今晚还能起飞吗?
Still taking passengers tonight?
凡奈斯机场,8点半
Van Nuys Airport,8:30.
今天的事只是生意,
Look,with everything that happened today,nothing personal,
我会打理你们的钱财,然后我就走
I'll take care of your finances and then I'm out.
- 好 - 这样可以
- Okay.- Fair enough.
我现在正站在洛杉矶市区
I'm standing about a block awayfrom the Monroe office building
距离门罗大楼一个街区
in downtown Los Angeles
一小时前一位洛杉矶警察在楼里被枪杀
where an LAPD detectivewas shot and killed about an hour ago.
准时到来
Right on time.
目击者称
Witnesses describe...
杰西打死了警察 又丢了钱,是什么感觉?
So,Jesse,how'd it feel losing that money,shooting that cop?
- 老鬼行了
- Ghost.Easy.- What?
目前无法确认,但嫌疑犯
Now,we can't confirm,at this hour,but the suspect...
老鬼,你现在不假装我们是朋友了?
Ghost,we ain't gotta act like we friends anymore,do we?
喂,生意是生意 钱是钱
Hey,business is business.Money is money.
我可没说过我们是朋友
I never said we were friends.
- 不过我和莉莉是朋友 - 你过来!
- Now,me and Lilli,however.- Come here!You wanna...
别激动!杰克,杰克!
Hey!Take it easy!Hey,Jake,Jake,Jake!
别激动!他不值得你上火
Hey,come on,take it easy!He's not worth it,all right?
都把人叫上 离开这里吧
All right,let's get the fellas and get out of here.
我来了 哪个房间?
I'm here.Which room?
1116 好
1116.A'ight.
威尔士,你在哪儿?有什么情况?
Hey,Welles,where you at?You got a 20?
我知道你能听见 回话
Come on,man,I know you're out there.Pick up.
我们都担心你
We're worried about you.Where you...
好了,各位,我们走吧
All right,fellas,we're good.We're out of here.
下面这样 如果谁想去
So,here's the deal.Anyone wants to fly with...
- 老鬼呢?- 在卫生间
- Where's Ghost?- In the bathroom.
叫他来
Get Ghost for me.
今晚,斯考特,8:30,凡奈斯机场
Tonight,Scott,8:30,Van Nuys Airport,all right?
飞机准备好了 带上护照,行李,手枪
Plane's ready.Bring your passports,your bags,and your guns.
老鬼?喂!
Ghost?Hey!
有什么需要,给我们打电话
If you need anything,make sure you give us a call.
他在干什么,洗澡吗?
What's he doing,taking a shower?What's going on in here?
- 怎么了?- 淋浴开着
- What was that?- Shower's on.
他不见了!
Hey,he's gone!
- 我就说过!我就说过!
- I told you!I told you!- What?
- 不至于吧!
- I don't know about this.- Damn!
- 他去哪儿了?
- What are you talking about?- Where'd he go?
- 我就知道有问题!
- I knew this was a bad idea!- Damn it!
我们离开这里,我们离开这里
Let's get out of here,let's get out.
天!
Oh,shit!
拿出自动步枪!
Take out the automatic!
杰西!
Jesse!
杰克,你怎么样?
Hey,Jake,you okay?
起来!快起来!快!
Get up,man,get up!Come on,buddy!Come on,man,come on!
- 走后门!- 杰西,杰克,我们走!
- Out the back!- Jesse,Jake,let's go!
我们快走!
Come on,let's go!
走 我随后就来
Go.I'm coming.
走!
Go!
快,快!
Come on,come on!
A J呢?他在哪儿?
Where's A.J?Where's A.J?Where's...
卧倒!
Down,get down!
- 他们是什么人?- 听口音是俄国人!
- Shit!Who are these guys?- Sounds like Russians!
杰克!去看看走廊
Jake!Check the hallway.
我们把床抬起来,来!
Let's put these beds up,let's go!
走廊有人守着!
We got a shotgun in the hallway!
卧倒,卧倒!
Stay low,stay low!
该死!我没子弹了!
Shit!I'm out of ammo!I'm out,I'm out!
杰克呢?
Where's Jake?
我们该走了,各位 我们该走了
We gotta go,fellas.We gotta go.
老鬼让我们和俄国人火拼
Ghost set us up against the Russians.
混蛋,他肯定也把计划提供给了他们
Son of a bitch,he must've sold them on the same plan.
所以他们把调度员给他
That's why they gave him the dispatcher
仓促抢劫 就是为了让我们先动手
and that big hurry-up was just to get us to do the job first.
- 对,我们上当了 - 彻底上当了
- Yeah,and we bought it.- Yeah,all of it.
这一片很快要封锁了
Shit,the heat's gonna be coming down now.
是啊 我们机场见
I know.See you at the airport.
莉莉?莉莉?
Lilli?Lilli?
坚持住,亲爱的 起来
Hold on,baby.Oh,God,baby,get up.Baby.
天啊,亲爱的,醒醒
Oh,my God,baby,wake up.Oh,just...
该死的,钱不见了!
Goddamn,the money's gone!
杰西,来帮帮我!
Jesse,help me!Help me!
老鬼,我要杀了你
Ghost.Ghost,I'm gonna kill you.Oh,God.
杰克,有人来了
Jake,we got company.
杰克,我们必须走了
Jake,we gotta go.We have to go.
天,老鬼
Oh,God.Ghost.
我们是洛杉矶警察慢慢走出房子
Los Angeles Police Department.Exit the building slowly.
限你们20秒钟之内走出来
You have 20 seconds to come out.
杰克,我看错了老鬼
Look,Jake.I was wrong about Ghost.
对不起
I'm sorry,man.
这不怪你
It's not your fault.
杰西你不必陪我冒险
Jesse,you ain't gotta be down with me on this one.
你要考虑自己未来的生活
You got your own life to think about,man.
我说过了,绝不再回监狱
I already told you.I'm never going back.
这就是我的生活
And this is my life.
我的车在后面你的车呢?
My car's out back.Where's yours?
在前面
In front.
我们坐你的车
Let's take yours.
知道你会这么说
Thought you'd say that.
准备好了吗,兄弟?
You ready,bro?
我们兄弟一起走吧
Just me and you,big brother.Let's go.
- 内奥米 - 戈登!
- Naomi.- G!
- 你干什么?来 - 戈登!
- What are you doing?Come here.- G!
你怎么在这儿?没事吧?
What are you doing?Are you all right?
- 他们不让我离开 - 我们必须走
- They won't let me in your building.- We've gotta go.
来,我们上车
Come on,let's get in the car.All right.
- 我只想回老家 - 好
- Just wanna go home.- All right.
看见你了
There you are.
- 说 - 我快到机场了
- Talk to me.- I'm almost to the airport.
我也是
Yeah,me,too.
我在琢磨一件事 听我简单说说?
Hey,I'm tripping.Hear me out right quick,all right?
怎么了?
Yeah,what's up?
老鬼一开始就在耍弄我们
Ghost has had the jump on us from the get-go,right?
那他为什么把我们都干掉
So,why would he take us all out
却只满足于得到04年的那笔钱呢?
and then only settle for the cash from the '04 job?
- 他不会的 - 除非
- He wouldn't.- Unless...
- 他打算把钱都拿走 - 钱都在斯考特那里
- Man,he plans on taking all the money.- Shit,Scott.Scott has all the money.
没错 我这就去 跟着你去
Exactly.I'm on my way.I'm right behind you.
我知道很晚了 让他和我在银行会面
I know this is a little last-minute.Have him meet me at the bank.
斯考特,快接电话 接电话
Come on,Scott,pick up.Scott,pick up.
我今晚就去
Yeah,I'm coming in tonight.
你明天早上9点要有空,好吗?
You have to make yourself available at 9:00 a.m.Tomorrow,all right?
你能做到吗?
Can you do that?
我是斯考特 现在我不在
You've reached Scott.I'm away from my cell.
斯考特,快接电话 真是的
Oh,God.No,Scott,pick up.Damn it.
好
All right.
好了我们走吧
Okay.Let's get out of here.
今天累坏了 能给我倒一杯酒吗?
It's been a long day.Can you pour me a Scotch?
你去哪儿? 你一定要独吞啊,老鬼?
Yeah,where are you going?You just had to have it all,didn't you,Ghost?
- 我只是拿走我的钱!- 是吗?
- I'm just taking what's mine!- Oh,yeah?
今天在街上就该打死你
I should've shot you on the street today.
不,5年前你就该把我打死在楼梯上
Naw,you should've shot me five years ago on that fire escape.
是你被抓住了,老鬼!你被抓住了!
You got caught,Ghost!You got caught!
你知道我们的约定!
You knew the game when you was playing it!
你们把我丢下不管!
You left me back there to die like I was shit!
不是不管你!
You ain't shit,Ghost!
我帮你把队伍组织起来!
I helped you put this crew together!
你现在又想拆散队伍吗?
So what?Now you wanna take it apart?
放下武器!警察!放下武器!
Drop the weapon!Drop it!Police!Put them down!
- 放下!- 放下!
- Put them down!- Stay out of this!
- 这是我俩的恩怨
- Better listen to him,cop.- It's between me and him.
你干涉的话,我把你也杀了
If you interfere,I'm gonna kill you,too.
- 最后说一遍,放下武器!
- Last time,drop them!- Shit.
我还能怎么做,戈登?
What you expect me to do,G?Huh?
拿走了我的钱 抢走了我的女人
You took my money.Took my bitch from me.
把我赶出了队伍?
Just put me out the crew,huh?
我以为我会忘记从前?
What you thought I was gonna do?Let that shit go?
你被抓住了!
You got caught!
好 我现在明白了
Yeah.A'ight.I see now.
你只看成公事公办
It's all business for you.
但我觉得是私人恩怨
Well,this shit just got real personal.
- 你该等着我的 - 他干得太快了
- Should've waited for me,G.- The shit went too fast.
等等,等等
Hold,hold it,hold it,hold it.
别动!你别动!
Don't move!Don't you move!
那天就是你跟踪我们
You're that cop with the little girl.
你不该插手的
You should've stayed out of this.
- 我们带上钱走吧 - 好
- Let's get that money and get out of here.- Yeah.
救护中心
Emergency dispatch.
对
Yeah.
有警察受伤 凡奈斯机场12号机库
You got an officer down.Van Nuys Airport,hangar 12.
我中枪了需要救助
I've been shot and I need help.
马上就到
Units en route.
我想帮忙
I want help.
戈登?我们现在回老家吗?
G?Are we going home now?
对,我们回老家
Yeah,baby.We're going home.
情况怎么样?
Are we good,brother?
一切都好
All signs point to it.